{
    "subject": "resource/Lake_Tegel",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Berlin",
    "human_readable": "Lake Tegel is located in Berlin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8766703009605408,
            "question": "Where is Lake Tegel located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947820425033569,
            "question": "Is Lake Tegel in Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7279478907585144,
            "question": "Can you find a lake in Berlin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7091501951217651,
            "question": "Name a lake in Berlin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6854026317596436,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Lake Tegel is situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6571868658065796,
            "question": "Lake Tegel is a feature of which city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6480400562286377,
            "question": "Which German city contains Lake Tegel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5120649933815002,
            "question": "What city is home to Lake Tegel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44526946544647217,
            "question": "In what European country would you find Lake Tegel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30780017375946045,
            "question": "What major European city has Lake Tegel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lake Tegel is located in Berlin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2985_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what European country would you find Lake Tegel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2985_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is home to Lake Tegel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2985_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which German city contains Lake Tegel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2985_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2985_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Lake Tegel is located in Berlin\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Lake Tegel as being located within the city or district of Berlin, specifically mentioning it as being situated in the northwest of Berlin in Reinickendorf."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Lake Tegel is located in Berlin, specifically mentioning its location within the Reinickendorf borough and northwest of the city."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}